1 2 3
[music]
Okay guys, we're in the warehouse now
because Lisa wants to get
vacation nails done and her nails
actually didn't look
so nice anymore.
Her nails are being done right now, and
here is the design she
wanted.
It won't
look exactly the same, of course, because these are
adult-sized earth nails, because they are
really long and all that.  Ner won't
make them any longer.  The only thing
Nissa wants is the color, so pink,
and she also wants to make this flower,
and Elif is there too.  I am here, and I
am here too.  [music]
[music]
Okay guys, Nisa's nails are now finished.
That's what they look like.  As you can see, it's
not like in the picture; they're just
short.  But she has
a flower here in the middle and here too. I have to say,
I think it turned out really well,
as I said.
That goes well with your outfit
somehow.  Yes.
[music]
Should we take the big wagon?
No, let the little one take it from inside.
Yes, let the smaller one take it.
[music]
I'll take a small tube of toothpaste with me.
Micellar water in miniature.  Should I also
bring some skincare products?
No, we can bring our skincare products as usual
.   A
small bottle of washing gel is very important.  Yes,
for washing your face.  We'll use Mermaid shower gel
.
my hand.
Oh right.
N said she needs shampoo
and conditioner now.  Should we take this with us?
Look, it's shampoo and
conditioner in one.
No, but [clears throat]
here is shampoo and conditioner.
Yes, of
couse.  Okay, then we'll take the
shampoo and conditioner.  We have now
decided on these three.  I hope that should be
enough.
My skincare bag and my
airplane bag.  First of all, my
Snakebox.  I did that with Nisa yesterday
.  Very important: power bank,
chewing gum, my passport, a light for
videos, my house keys
so we can go inside when we get home, AirPods,
deodorant, hand sanitizer, lip balm, and another
face spray.
Come on. Okay guys, I can't
film anymore now because I
really need to hurry, because
our taxi to the airport is coming soon and I have
n't even packed my clothes yet and I
think I only have half an
hour left.  We're packing my suitcase now.
I'll show you now which clothes
I'm taking with me.  So, we're only there for 5 days
, so I'm
not taking that much with me, but I did go
shopping, bought a few outfits and I'll show them to
you now.  I'm also taking this
T-shirt that I wore today.  Do
I still have this T-shirt?  That's really
great, guys.  I think that [music] is so
awesome.  Maybe I'll take these
trousers with me too.  Guys, I've been wanting bell-bottoms for a while now
.  I'd been wanting it the whole time, so
I just went to H&M and ate it
.  Guys, she's so awesome.
I'll wear that with this top.  Was there a
bag for that, I'll
carry it.  Guys, we have to leave in two
hours or so and I'm packing
my beauty bag with you now, [music] because
I brewed it today, so
I didn't pack it last night
.  So, I only packed a few things for
when I go to shower.
One of these Leing Cream sunscreens
for the face, one of the lotion deodorants, and one of the
spray deodorants.  Now we come to my
make-up.
Fun, these two things from Spray, it
cools down so [music] really great.  It contains
coconut.  He's really awesome,
guys.  This brown mascara and this
brown-black one.  It's waterproof,
that's why I'm taking it with me,
because it's very good, because [music] is
waterproof because of swimming and stuff.
My Frackle Pen.  I need to get my
frackles sorted, because I don't have any real ones,
unfortunately.  My blush is from Glorcipe.  I
love him.  Take this palette with you,
I've had it for a while now, but
it's really good.  There are so
many different things in there.
Eyelash curler.  All I need now is
my dental floss here and then I'm
done.
Alright guys, we're ready for
the airport now.  Elif has such a big
suitcase.  Okay guys,
you have a big suitcase too.
Yes, that's right.  And our two are
actually heavy.  Nisa's, you
took a small one.
15 kg.   What
?
15 kg.
You only weigh 15 kg?
Okay,
so Elif, I think you're about
40. I'd say let's go to the
airport, because we're
already a little late.
[music]
Okay guys, so Elips' suitcase weighs
27 kg.  Let's see if mine
or hers is heavier.  The Elips suitcase is
so heavy that we now have to pay something
.
Nisa's suitcase.  My God, Nisa only weighs 12
kg.
Ah, 24. Mine is okay.  I
think we're allowed exactly 24 or 23.
On the plane we were
given a coloring book and also a pen
thing with a sharpener attached, but
somehow Nisa wasn't really interested,
even though it was actually for her.  I
found it somehow more interesting, but
yes, we definitely
ate something there.
Guys, we're on the plane now and
the funny thing is, I'm not actually sitting
next to Nisa.  So, I
actually have a seat that's way in the back
, in the last
row, but there was a man sitting there who was
so nice, he even swapped seats with me,
and
unfortunately,
yes, that's why I'm now sitting next to Nisa.
We are sitting together.  Elif is unfortunately somewhere else
.  Unfortunately, she didn't
make it.   This
is my snack box and I'm going to show
you mine now.  Nice has
also made one, and you have to
say which one is better.  So, we
have here some poisonous dried
passion fruit, we have poisonous dried
lychee, we have chocolate rice cakes,
gummy bears, dried strawberries or something
, banana chips and we have
sweet popcorn, unfortunately not salty.  I actually love it
when sweet and salty
are mixed, but this is just too sweet.
Now you have to show your snack box.
Yeah, mine's cooler, guys.
Guys, this is the Snakebox from ISA.
But somehow it's completely confused
.  Well, I already don't like your
snack box.  I think we
can all say that my snack box
is better, right?  Please comment with your
honest opinion.  Just a sandwich.
Oh God.
[music]
Hello my dears and
welcome.  Fun.  Do it again.
Okay guys, I'm going to give you a
room tour of our villa here on
Santorini.  Here, for example, is a
couch where you can sit.  We now have
a kitchen that we've
actually never used.  Here
we have a table where we have
n't even sat down yet.
Here's a staircase.  We've
actually never used that, because
Nisa's room is up here.   Let me
show you this.
[music]
So, nobody slept in here.
Yes,
so if anyone wants to, you're welcome to
come.  Oh,
I would be careful with that.
Bathroom.  I use the bathroom pretty much all the time
.  There's
a shower back here, then my room and
Misa's room.  Elif sleeps
sometimes too.  We actually share that responsibility.
Exactly.  First, there's Elif's bathroom,
and then there's Eli's room where she
sleeps.  The best part is coming, guys.
[music]
Seriously
guys, this pool is so awesome.  Firstly,
because it's deep, and secondly, because it's
big; you can swim there so well
.  Where Elif is, we have a
warpool.  The great thing about it is, it's
warm.  If you press this
button,
bubbles come out, and yeah, it
's definitely really cool, and the
view, guys, it looks so beautiful.
Oh, there's an MF fin.
We are now getting ready for the
first day.  We were already in the pool.
We didn't show you that just now, but um
yeah,
we'll show it to you later, but we were having too much
fun.  We forgot the
camera.  We're definitely getting
ready for our first day on
Santurigi.
[cheers]
No way, that was crap.
Okay guys, Nisa is putting on her makeup now,
or rather, getting ready.  She's applying
sunscreen right now, which is very important
.  Very good indeed.  I'm getting
ready now, and then we'll be
off.  Elif said she has
a surprise for me today.  I'm
curious what the surprise is.  I
think it's probably about
food anyway, because Elef talks about
food all the time.  These are our outfits.
N and I are wearing matching outfits today.  We
are both pink.  So, these are our
shoes.
[music]
Wow,
but I feel a bit overdriven.
No, it's awesome.
Okay, guys, so our car is
here now.  Okay, we're getting started now, and Elif still
has something planned.  She
scares me a little, but um,
oh my god, did you hit your head
?   Haven't had a drink all day
,
guys.  They even gave us water
.  They're really
nice here.
Ah, delicious.
Turn around, Jule.  Look ahead.
[music]
I don't see the way, guys.  Do you see
him?   Yes
.  No, B, because you're shining your light on us.
Yes, but I'm about to fall off the cliff here
.  [laughter]
Absolutely, yes, we're wearing bathrobes
because we were cold, don't be surprised.
And Jule and Lena were just
visiting us.  We ate something.  We
forgot to film anything in the restaurant
because we were talking so much.
Lena and Elif simply
exchanged numbers and made a plan
for Jule and me to meet up.   Yes
.   Yes
.   Bye everyone
, see you
tomorrow.   See you in the
morning.
[music]
My sisters and I love
to eat Assaib.  Seriously, we're addicted to it
.  Whenever we
are in Germany, we always eat this at home
.  There is a shop that
I believe was invented, and it's located
here.  That's where we'll go and I
think you'll hear Els Sch people the whole time
[laughter]
I have such a how can you see that?  I have
a slight heel.  They're making
noises all the time.   I
'm very curious to see if the Asaiball will
top ours in our city in Germany, because we love it
and Jula said it's the
best.  We always eat it with
peanut butter, and there they have it with
pistachio butter.  Pisa.  You can turn the camera
off again.  Yes.
Oh right.   Yes
.
Turn them off.
Guys, this is the shop Jule was talking about
.  We're already here.
That's the purple one.  Guys, look
who's here.
Hi.
So, this is the Asaib, where Juli
said she's the best Miss
Pistazus, right?  I now have a little bit of
Pro.   I
'm really curious.  [music]
[music]
Actually, it's completely different, much fruitier.
This is much better than peanut butter.   What do
you say?
[music]
Okay guys, so we're going to
Jule's hotel now because we
have a surprise there.
Yes, but Nisa is riding with me.
Nisa will now ride with Jule because
she has a free seat, since Lena did
n't come along.
[music]
Okay guys, Nisa and Jule are already here.
Elif and I have just arrived, we
came here on the subway.   It looks
like a cave.
So we're now at Jule's.
Yes, how am I supposed to do that?
And we want to open this curtain
so we have more light for
filming videos, and
Lena has always done that.
Very good.
Lena, how did you do that?
[Music] doesn't let it happen.
[music]
Okay.  Okay. And now I open it, right
?
Oh my God, guys, the freak-out.
Wait,
guys, the view is so traumatic.
Wow.  Wow,
I'm shocked.
Dude, your view is really
amazing.
That's a crazy view.  Wow,
guys, I don't know if you can
see it, but it's very windy today.
We don't even know if we can
surprise ourselves at all.
I also agree that it's far too
dangerous.
Also?
Who else is against it?
I'm in favor of that too, right
?
That it's too dangerous.
Yes, it really is too dangerous.
So, above all, that's not
dangerous.
Yes, but Lena, look how windy it is.
Boom, boom, boom.  You could still sit out.
El
Ja, ja, stunning.   Are
you all crazy?  What are you doing?
Here we go.  We are all ready.
Are you ready for the surprise?   Yes
.
Okay, then I would say take a taxi.
[music]
So, we now need to decide
who sits in the front.  Okay, guys, so we're getting started
now.  Nisa is sitting here.
Lena and Jule are also sitting in the back.
Nisa, are you excited?   Yes
.
OK.  Lena, you.
Yes.
Jule.
OK.
[music]
Guys, we've found a shop
where I don't really
want to buy anything.  I wonder, what's there
butter here?
No, not butter.
People think of butter as bread.
Squishes.
Squishies, somehow, these butter
squishies.  That's what she meant.
We'll take one of those with us.
Take.
I don't know.  Nie will take
this butter with him now.  Oh right.  And we'll take another one of these with us
.  Which would
you prefer, right or left?  I
somehow think the one on the left looks better.   That's it
.  Yes.
Okay, then hold that in your
hand too.  Did I really pay €60 for all of this?
We don't talk about it.
Nisa and I were on holiday here in
Santorini and we
saw a shop that sells XXL dumplings
.  You have to imagine, they
're actually so small.  Look,
normally they're so small and this one
is so big.  That's really crazy.
It cost €50, so €48.  I
hope there's something amazing in there now,
because otherwise we're really being
ripped off.  We're saying €50 for that is just how it is;
everything here is unfortunately
very expensive.  What color would you
like it to be?  Either
a golden one, well
, at that price it should really
be gold,
pink or something.
Pink or blue.  Blue.
OK.  Don't be surprised if we're not
looking at the camera, because we're
also recording a video, hence 1 Z
3. [gasps]
Green.
Oh, watch out, watch out.  [gasps]
But the color is [ __ ].
The color is really awful.  I thought there would be
gold.
I also said I didn't want
green.  got himself another one of those squishy toys
.  Such squishy butter.  Butter,
how much did it
cost?  It cost €7 instead of €9.
I know,
but still €7 for a butter,
and right now for the time being.
I think he's so cool.  So, I think it's kind of... So
guys, we're swimming now and
Nisa has put on the blue fin and
she tells me to put on the pink one
.  A children's size, which is
smaller.  It doesn't even fit me.
But I don't feel like moving out again.
Look how cool.
I'm not wearing the pink one.  Take that
off.
What does the pink one look like?
Pinky
pinky.  My feet don't fit in.
I've got it.
Okay, I've got it.
My foot doesn't quite fit in.
Oh my God.  Oh my
[music]
Yes, great.  [music]
Wow.
Oh, how warm.
It is warm.  The other pool was so
cold.
Yes,
[laughter] do
n't drop it.
Okay guys, we're going to take a short
swimming break now.  We've ordered food now
.  A bowl with rice, I
think coleslaw, shrimp, and eggs.  So,
really healthy in May.  We
also have sushi, [ahem] because, folks, the
sushi here is so delicious.  Unique,
oh, that looks a bit special.   There's
a role in it.  This is the
first time we've experienced this.
Exactly, we already know that.
We ate this with Jul yesterday.   Yummy
.  It's so delicious.
And I would now say, bon appétit,
and then we'll continue swimming.
Today is really like a
swimming day.
We're just swimming.
Yes.
My nose has given up too.   Yes
.